{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/5127","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5127","name":"Panera Bread-RenCen","address":"400 Renaissance Dr.","zipcode":"48243","owner":"Panera Bread LLC","licenseNumber":"083426","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"150","coords":"-83.04072,42.32982","geojson":{"id":"5127","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.04071807,42.32982254]},"properties":{"name":"Panera Bread-RenCen","owner":"Panera Bread LLC","address":"400 Renaissance Dr.","zipcode":"48243","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"083426","establishmentid":"5127","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"150","most_recent_license_date":"12/4/2022"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3240","name":"Potbelly Sandwich Shop","address":"400 Renaissance Ctr. Ste. 1304","zipcode":"48226"},{"establishmentid":"1420","name":"McDonald's Ren-Joi, Inc.","address":"200 Renaissance Center","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"2114","name":"Sodexho Management","address":"200 Rennaissance Center","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"2008","name":"Ren Cen Subway Foods LLC","address":"200 Renaissnace Center","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"1151","name":"Gyroland, L.L.C.","address":"200 Renaissnace Center","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"1359","name":"Burger King Corp #13332","address":"200 Renaissance Center A-1042","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"1860","name":"That Sandwich Place","address":"200 Rennaissanc Center A-8320","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"1135","name":"Detroit Marriott Main Kitchen Hotel","address":"400 Rennaissance Center","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"1156","name":"Renaissance Club","address":"200 Renaissance Center A-3600","zipcode":"48243"},{"establishmentid":"3241","name":"Maui Wowi","address":"400 Renaissance","zipcode":"48226"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"57376","inspectionDate":"2022-02-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\n        \n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Held past time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"CHEMICAL STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."}]},{"inspectionid":"56462","inspectionDate":"2021-10-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"54280","inspectionDate":"2021-02-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"53493","inspectionDate":"2020-03-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"51290","inspectionDate":"2020-03-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"COVID19-temp closed","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"49681","inspectionDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Ready to eat, potentially hazardous food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Beyond consume by date","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.114","violationDescription":"A chemical SANITIZER used in a SANITIZING solution for a manual or\nmechanical operation shall meet these limits or as otherwise approved: (P)\n\tChlorine        ppm           pH<10             pH<8\n\t\t      25              120 F              120 F\n\t\t      50              100 F              75 F\n\t\t     100              55 F               55 F\n                 Iodine           a concentration of between 12.5 and 25 ppm and minimum temp of 75 F and pH of 5 or less or meets manufacturer's specifications. (P)\n\n                Quats            minimum temperature of 75 F, hardness of 500 ppm or less and meet manufacturers use directions. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Chlorine solution concentration","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Below 25 ppm","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\n        \n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\n        \n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clearly marked or identified with time control","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2010-01-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.12","violationDescription":"(A) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking and baking EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours. This section does not apply to hot oil cooking and filtering EQUIPMENT if it is cleaned as specified in Subparagraph 4-602.11(D)(6).   \n(B) The cavities and door seals of microwave ovens shall be cleaned at least every 24 hours by using the manufacturer's recommended cleaning procedure.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Baking and cooking equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not cleaned","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FLOOR","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"45827","inspectionDate":"2019-04-06T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\n\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"43365","inspectionDate":"2018-09-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-202.15","violationDescription":"FOOD packages shall be in good condition and protect the integrity of the contents so that the FOOD is not exposed to ADULTERATION or potential contaminants. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food package(s)","subItem":"Cans","problemDescription":"Dented, dented on seam or swollen","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"hair/beard net","problemDescription":"Not worn on face","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide beard net."},{"violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Adulterated/contaminated","subProblem":"","location":"COOK LINE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]},{"inspectionid":"41372","inspectionDate":"2018-02-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Water source and system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water pressure to meet demand of use."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Remove items from handsink.  Do not store items at handsink."},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"39179","inspectionDate":"2017-07-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"BACK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store toxics below and away from all other items."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SANDWICH STATION","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"0001-01-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"DRY STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37187","inspectionDate":"2016-11-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.19","violationDescription":"If time only, rather than time in conjunction with temperature, is used as the public health control for a working supply of POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  before cooking, or for READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  that is displayed or held for service for immediate consumption:   \n(1)   Written procedures are required to be prepared in advance, maintained in the establishment, and made available to the REGULATORY AUTHORITY upon request.(Pf)\n(2)   The FOOD shall be marked to indicate the time that is 4 hrs past the point in which food is removed from temperature control, or 6 hrs if the temperature is maintained below 70°F. (Pf)\n(3)   Food in unmarked containers or in containers that exceed the time limit are to be discarded. (P)\n        \n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Time controlled food(s)","subItem":"potentially hazardous food(s) before cooking","problemDescription":"Without time control mark","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide clear easy to read time marks."},{"violationCode":"7-102.11","violationDescription":"Working containers used for storing POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIALS such as cleaners and SANITIZERS taken from bulk supplies shall be clearly and individually identified with the common name of the material. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Working containers-toxics","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not labeled as to content","subProblem":"","location":"CHEMICAL STORAGE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2011-01-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"PREP AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-13T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5127"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}